{"data":[{"question":"Frank starts work _____ dawn.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Columbus discovered America _____ 1492.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Mr. and Mrs. Peters went to Hawaii _____ their anniversary.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Please serve the souffl\u00e9 _____ once.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- At once: immediately or without delay","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Brenda was born _____ the fourth of July.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Mr. Hillis will arrive here _____ Monday morning.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"George has his Spanish class _____ the morning.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Use \"in\": with parts of the day\n\u2022 in the morning\n\u2022 in the evening","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"Horses were the principal means of transportation _____ nineteenth century.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"It is sometimes difficult to calm children down _____ bedtime.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"},{"question":"____ 10 years most appliances will have basic intelligence.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"- Prepositions of time: at, in, on:\n+ In: for months, years, centuries, long periods\n+ At: for a precise time (at 3 o'clock, at noon, at sunrise, at the moment)\n+ On: for days and dates (on Sunday, on 6 March, on Christmas Day, on my birthday...)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"38","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"2"}]}